UX/UI DESIGNER

PRECIOUS ENWEREM

4379287832

Enweremprecious16@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/precious-enwerem-246871170 · Portfolio

A highly creative and innovative UI/UX designer based in Toronto, Canada with the determination to learn and enhance my design sense. I aim to help clients achieve their goal and create meaningful experience and opportunity through my designs.

EXPERIENCE

AUGUST 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021 (CONTRACT)

UX/UI DESIGNER, DAVITO SERVICES

Davito services is an immigration company based in Brampton, Canada. As the UX/UI designer my core activities included:

- Gathering and evaluating user requirements.
- o Researching, creating wire frames, site maps, user flow diagrams and prototypes.
- Creating and presenting hi–fi prototypes.

NOVEMBER 2021 – JANUARY 2022 (CONTRACT)

UX/UI DESIGNER, REVOLUTION RECORDS

Revolution records is a record label based in Lagos, Nigeria. As the UX/UI designer my core activities included:

- Designing the look and feel of the website.
- Working directly with the software developers to create an easy to navigate website.

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, BILL GOSLING OUTSOURCING

Bill gosling outsourcing is an outsourcing and account management services based in Newmarket, Canada.

- Answering probing questions to customers and providing advice over the phone.
- o Identifying and solving problems while providing technical and troubleshooting support.
- o Handling inbound calls in a professional, efficient and courteous manner.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2018

WEST AFRICA SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE EXAMINATION, CALEB INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, LAGOS, NIGERIA

2018 - 2019

DIPLOMA, GREAT LAKES COLLEGE OF TORONTO

2021

UX DESIGN CERTIFICATE, GOOGLE UX CERTIFICATE

SKILLS

Software

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Canvas
- Illustrator
- In Vision
- Sketch

Others

- Story Boarding
- Flow Chart

Design

- Design Research
- User Interface
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Web Design
- Interaction design